[
  {
    "question": "The 4 Harry Potter houses",
    "answer": ["red", "blue", "green", "yellow"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Russia's flag",
    "answer": ["red", "white", "blue"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Brazil's flag",
    "answer": ["blue", "yellow", "green", "white"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Canada's flag",
    "answer": ["red", "white"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ukraine's flag",
    "answer": ["blue", "yellow"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Jamaica'a flag",
    "answer": ["black", "yellow", "green"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Italy's flag",
    "answer": ["green", "white", "red"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Japan's flag",
    "answer": ["red", "white"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ireland's flag",
    "answer": ["green", "white", "orange"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Germany's flag",
    "answer": ["black", "red", "yellow"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Argentina's flag",
    "answer": ["blue", "white", "yellow"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Austria's flag",
    "answer": ["red", "white"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Google's logo",
    "answer": ["blue", "red", "yellow", "green"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Colors that stimulate hunger",
    "answer": ["red", "yellow"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Olympic Flag rings",
    "answer": ["black", "blue", "red", "yellow", "green"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In a rainbow",
    "answer": ["red", "orange", "yellow", "green", "blue", "purple"]
  },
  {
    "question": "United Nations official colors",
    "answer": ["blue", "white"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Combined make green",
    "answer": ["blue", "yellow"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Olympic rings",
    "answer": ["blue", "yellow", "black", "green", "red"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Gloves of Cruella De Vil (Disney 1961)",
    "answer": ["red"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sea between Turkey and Russia",
    "answer": ["black"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Marge Simpson’s dress",
    "answer": ["green"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Golden Gate Bridge",
    "answer": ["red"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Google logo",
    "answer": ["red", "blue", "green", "yellow"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Swords in Star Wars",
    "answer": ["purple", "blue", "green", "red"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Clean’s eyebrows",
    "answer": ["white"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Most common eye color",
    "answer": ["brown"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Charlie Brown’s t-shirt (The Peanuts)",
    "answer": ["black", "yellow"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fur and eye color of albino rabbits",
    "answer": ["red", "white"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Curry",
    "answer": ["red", "green", "yellow"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ted Mosby’s boots",
    "answer": ["red"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Dory in Finding Nemo",
    "answer": ["black", "blue", "yellow"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Hogwarts express",
    "answer": ["red"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Hat and jacket of Paddington bear",
    "answer": ["blue", "red"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fairies in Sleeping Beauty (Disney 1959)",
    "answer": ["red", "blue", "green"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Logo of Domino’s Pizza",
    "answer": ["red", "blue", "white"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Nemo",
    "answer": ["black", "orange", "white"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Teletubbies",
    "answer": ["green", "yellow", "red", "purple"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tennis courts of the grand-slam tournaments",
    "answer": ["green", "blue", "red"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Dartboard",
    "answer": ["black", "green", "red", "white"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Gandalf in Lord Of The Rings",
    "answer": ["grey", "white"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Classic M&M’s colors",
    "answer": ["brown", "orange", "blue", "red", "green", "yellow"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Asparagus",
    "answer": ["green", "white", "purple"]
  },
  {
    "question": "’Another Brick In The Wall’ is a Song of…",
    "answer": ["pink"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Pikachu’s cheeks",
    "answer": ["red"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Candy in Candy Crush",
    "answer": ["red", "blue", "orange", "purple", "green", "yellow"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Pepsi logo",
    "answer": ["red", "blue", "white"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ikea logo",
    "answer": ["blue", "yellow"]
  }
]
